So I love hot sauce.
我喜欢辣酱
I literally just put it on every single thing
我吃什么都要涂辣酱
I can find around the house sometimes. From pizza to chicken wings.
只要是家里能找到的食物 从披萨到鸡翅
Even though it gives me terrible acid reflux.
即使我会有严重的反酸
It makes its way up to my throat
一直流到我的嗓子眼
and I literally feel like I'm gonna vomit.
我觉得马上要吐出来了
- So... - Oh, yeah. That, um, sucks.
- 所以 - 是啊 那太糟糕了
But I love it, so...
但我太喜欢辣酱了 所以
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- 是啊 - 是啊
Like, I love wasabi, but, um,
我喜欢芥末
Mexican spices would be too much for me.
但墨西哥辣酱对我来说还是太冲了
- Mmm. Yeah. I get that. - Yeah.
- 嗯 我懂 - 是啊
Yeah.
是啊
- What? - I had this crazy thought. I...
- 怎么了 - 我有个疯狂的想法
I just feel like... the women in our parents' generation,
我就是觉得我们父母那一代的女人
they just cared more about how they dressed
她们更在乎她们的穿着打扮
and just, kind of, how they looked.
和她们的外表
They were more into femininity.
她们更注重女性气质 你明白我的意思吗
You know what I mean?
但现在
Like, nowadays, I feel like girls,
我觉得女生们
they just wear oversized everything, like it's a blanket.
都喜欢穿宽大的衣服 像是罩了个毯子一样
Do you know what I mean? You know what I'm saying, right?
你懂我的意思吗 你知道我在说什么 对吧
It's like... 'Cause I think you would just look great in a dress.
因为我觉得你穿裙子会很好看
Not that you don't look good in a sweater,
并不是说你穿毛衣不好看
- but I mean, if you were... - You guys okay?
- 但我的意思是 如果你 - 还需要什么吗
Uh, yeah. Um, pretty much done, actually. Thank you.
没事 我们差不多吃完了 谢谢你
Cool. Yeah, we'll just get this wrapped up then.
好的 剩下的都打包吧
- Thank you. - You're welcome.
- 谢谢 - 别客气
Oh, did you bring cash?
你带现金了吗
Yeah. You reminded me, so...
你提醒我了 那
My brother is coming into town.
我弟弟要来城里看我了
If it's cool, I'm just gonna snag these leftovers
如果可以的话 我想带些剩菜回去
- and, uh, I guess I'll just let you leave... - Cool. No. Yeah.
- 你可以 - 好的 没关系
a couple bucks less on the tip.
少付几块钱小费
If that makes sense.
这样很公平吧
Your scarf is dipping into the noodles.
你的围巾浸在面条里了
Oh, fuck! Shit!
可恶 该死
I love this scarf. Um... Excuse me? Excuse me.
我很喜欢这条围巾的 不好意思 服务员
Quick, come. Hi, do you have sparkling water?
快点 过来下 你好 你们有苏打水吗
- Sparkling. - Mmm-hmm. Yeah.
- 苏打水 - 有
- Bubble. You know bubbles? - Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- 气泡水 你知道气泡吧 - 知道
And a lemon, please?
再加片柠檬 谢谢
I don't know if she understood what I said.
我不知道她是否明白我说的话
I don't think she speaks English.
她可能不会说英语
That was, uh, that was fun.
今晚很开心
You're really cute.
你很可爱
- Thank you. - Yeah. We should do this again sometime.
- 谢谢 - 真的 我们应该找个时间再约
Yeah, look, Chad, um... -Yeah.
- 好吧 听着 查德 - 嗯
Oh. I... I don't think we're really a match. You know?
我觉得我们不太合适
I was literally just being polite.
我只是出于礼貌而已
You're not even my type, to be honest, so...
老实说 你甚至不是我喜欢的类型 所以
- Okay. - Oh, that's funny? "Ha-ha, it's hilarious"? Yeah.
- 好的 - 很好笑吗 哈哈 真搞笑
Okay. Good luck finding a guy, you stuck-up bitch.
好吧 祝你找到一个男人 你这个自大的婊子
What the fuck.
什么鬼